

PRONPUN PUKKALO Sales Coordinator

Date of birth 13 January 1992

Nickname Bow

pornpun.1301@gmail.com

© 0990551267

 66/396 Feung Villa Village Thepharak
 Road, Bang Muang Subdistrict, Mueang District, Samut Prakan Province 10270

PROFILE

Learning never ends. Give yourself a chance to try it. Always believe that new things must come out well. and want to use their experience and knowledge learned with interpersonal skills including the experience of working with others as well to develop the organization to achieve the goals.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree

2015-2018

University of Ramkhamhaeng Bankkok Faculty of Political Science, Business Administration

secondary school (4-6)

2010-2014

non-school education Khok Pho Chai District Khon Kaen Province

secondary school (1-3)

2004-2007

Khok Pho Chai Suksa School Khon Kaen Science - Mathematics

LANGUAGES

• Thai

• English

Korea

EXPERIENCE

Sales Coordinator

From May 2021 to Current | THAI DENTAL PRODUCTS (T.D.P.) CO.,LTD

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

Dental assistant

From 2016 to April 2021 | Simitives Srinakarin Hospital, Bangkok

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

Dental assistant

From December 2015 to November 2015 | Vejthani Hospital, Bangkok

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

CERTIFICATES

Nursing Assistant (NA) Courses

dental assistant course.

Training for elders in early childhood education level

Basic life support (BLS) training

Basic Firefighting Training

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Prrogram PeopleSoft
- Good team work

- Program Takcare
- Program Sap
- Have good human relations

Typing Thai,Eng 35-45 words/minute

INTERESTS

REFERENCES

Software Development

Mr. Kreangkrai keawmoonmuk

Phone: 0934477875

Email : keawmoonmuk.k@gmail.com